Preliminary Guide to the Hannah Green Papers M1030
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 3: Accession 2012-064
  - The Dead of the House pages 148-239 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Notes (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Golden Spark, Little Saint (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Notes (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Rosellen Brown on Hannah Green's The Dead of the House (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: Samuel Vaughan (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous Material (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - The New Yorker 1966 and 1969 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - The New Yorker 1970 and 1977 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - The New Yorker 2000 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Reviews of "Little Saint" (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Series 4. Newspaper clippings and reviews
  - Clippings (1) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Clippings (2) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Clippings & reviews (1) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Clippings & reviews (2) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Clippings & reviews: The Dead of the House 1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Bronxville Reporter Articles (Box 2, Folder 23)